Press Gang Publishers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Editorial files, 1976 - 2000; F-184-4; 1.5 m of textual records 5 photographs; General note: photographs located in sub-series 2, file 17.
  - Editorial correspondence, 1980 - 2000; F-184-4-2; 70 cm of textual records 5 photographs
    - Author correspondence - old titles, 1986 - 1987; F-184-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 184-13)
    - Author correspondence - various authors, 1986 - 2000; F-184-4-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 184-13)
    - Arnott, Joanne - Breasting the Waves, 1995 - 1996; F-184-4-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 184-13)
      Arnott, Joanne; Textual records
    - Baxter, Sheila - Still Raising Hell, 1996 - 1997; F-184-4-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 184-13)
      Baxter, Sheila; Textual records
    - Beckylane, vol. 1, 1994 - 1995; F-184-4-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 184-13)
      Beckylane; Textual records
    - Beckylane, vol. 2, 1994 - 1995; F-184-4-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 184-13)
    - Beckylane - memorandum of agreement, 1994; F-184-4-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
    - Berge, Marilyn and others (editors) - Common Ground: Stories by Women, 1980 - 1984; F-184-4-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
      Berge, Marilyn; Textual records
    - Berge, Marilyn and others (editors) - Common Ground: Stories by Women - anthologizing request, 1982 - 1983; F-184-4-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Prozac Highway, 1997; F-184-4-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook, 1993 - 1997; F-184-4-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon and Sheila Gilhoooly - Still Sane, 1984 - 1986; F-184-4-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
      Blackbridge, Persimmon; Gilhooly, Sheila; Textual records
    - Bociurkiw, Marusya - The Woman Who Loved Airports, 1986 - 1995; F-184-4-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
      Bociurkiw, Marusya; Textual records
    - Briskin, Linda - The Day the Fairies Went on Strike, 1993 - 1992; F-184-4-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
      Briskin, Linda; Textual records
    - Cameron, Anne - Daughters of Copper Woman, 1980 - 1983; F-184-4-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
    - Cameron, Anne - Daughters of Copper Woman, 1983 - 1988; F-184-4-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
      Cameron, Anne; Textual records; Photographic materials
    - Cameron, Anne - Daughters of Copper Woman - large print edition, 1995 - 1996; F-184-4-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
    - Chrystos - correspondence, 1988 - 1996; F-184-4-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 184-14)
      Chrystos; Textual records
    - Decter, Ann - Honour, 1995 - 1997; F-184-4-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 184-15)
      Decter, Ann; Textual records
    - Decter, Ann - Paper, Scissors, Rock, 1991 - 1993; F-184-4-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 184-15)
    - Decter, Ann - Paper, Scissors, Rock - editing, 1992; F-184-4-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 184-15)
    - Douglas, Marion - Bending at the Bow, 1993 - 1995; F-184-4-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 184-15)
      Douglas, Marion; Textual records
    - Dykewomon, Elana - Beyond the Pale, 1995 - 1998; F-184-4-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 184-15)
    - Faith, Karlene - Unruly Women, 1992 - 1994; F-184-4-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 184-15)
      Faith, Karlene; Textual records
    - Field, Dorothy and Chudley, Carol Graham - The Accidental Squash, 1997 - 1998; F-184-4-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 184-15)
      Field, Dorothy; Chudley, Carol Graham; Graham, Carol; Textual records
    - Fuller, Janine and Stuart Blackley - Restricted Entry, 1995; F-184-4-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 184-15)
      Fuller, Janine; Stuart Blackey; Textual records
    - Fuller, Janine and Stuart Blackley - Restricted Entry 2nd edition, 1996; F-184-4-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 184-16)
    - Hughes, Nym, Yvette Perreault, and Yvonne Johnson - Stepping Out of Line, 1982 - 1987; F-184-4-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 184-16)
      Hughes, Nym; Perreault, Yvette; Johnson, Yvonne; Textual records
    - Jacob, Suzanne - Life After All, 1988 - 1993; F-184-4-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 184-16)
      Jacob, Suzanne; Textual records
    - Jones, Lizard - Two Ends of Sleep, 1996 - 1998; F-184-4-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 184-16)
      Jones, Lizard; Textual records
    - Kiss and Tell - Her Tongue on My Theory - proposal, 1993; F-184-4-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 184-16)
    - Lai, Larissa - When Fox is a Thousand, 1994 - 1996; F-184-4-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 184-16)
      Lai, Larissa; Textual records
    - Lee, SKY - publishing program solicitation, 1988 - 1994; F-184-4-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 184-16)
      Lee, Sky; Textual records
    - Maracle, Lee - I Am Woman, 1995 - 1996; F-184-4-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 184-17)
      Maracle, Lee; Textual records
    - Maracle, Lee - Sojourners and Sundogs, [199-?]; F-184-4-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 184-17)
    - Marlatt, Daphne - Telling It: Women and Language Across Cultures, 1989 - 1992; F-184-4-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 184-17)
      Marlatt, Daphne; Textual records
    - McLaughlin, Karen - Choral, 1994 - 1995; F-184-4-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 184-17)
      McLaughlin, Karen; Textual records
    - Moiseiwitsch, Carol - Women Draw (and cartoons), 1984 - 1985; F-184-4-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 184-17)
      Moiseiwitsch, Carol; Textual records
    - Mootoo, Shani - Out On Main Street, 1993 - 1994; F-184-4-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 184-17)
    - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night, 1994 - 1998; F-184-4-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 184-17)
    - Norgate, Sheila - Storm Clouds Over Party Shoes, 1996 - 1997; F-184-4-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 184-17)
      Norgate, Sheila; Textual records
    - Potrebenko, Helen - Sometimes They Sang, 1985 - 1986; F-184-4-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 184-17)
      Potrebenko, Helen; Textual records
    - Richler, Nancy - Throwaway Angels, 1995 - 1997; F-184-4-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 184-17)
      Richler, Nancy; Textual records
    - Shimrat, Irit - Call Me Crazy, 1996 - 1997; F-184-4-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
      Shimrat, Irit; Textual records
    - Silvera, Makeda - Her Head a Village, 1992 - 1994; F-184-4-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
      Silvera, Makeda; Textual records
    - Silvera, Makeda - The Revenge of Maria, 1998; F-184-4-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
    - Stonehouse, Cathy - The Words I Know, 1994 - 1995; F-184-4-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
      Stonehouse, Cathy; Textual records
    - Taste This - Boys Like Her, 1998; F-184-4-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
    - Tulchinsky, Karen - Love Runs Everything, 1997 - 1998; F-184-4-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
      Tulchinsky, Karen; Textual records
    - Van de Walle, Elly - Falling From Grace, 1983 - 1986; F-184-4-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
      Van de Walle, Elly; Textual records
    - Warland, Becky - Proper Definitions: Collected Theorograms, 1989 - 1990; F-184-4-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkey Puzzle, 1998; F-184-4-2-0-53 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
      Wong, Rita; Textual records
    - Wong, Rita - Monkey Puzzle - correspondence, vol. 1, 1998; F-184-4-2-0-54 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkey Puzzle - correspondence, vol. 2, 1998; F-184-4-2-0-55 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkey Puzzle - memorandum of agreement, 1998; F-184-4-2-0-56 (Archival box - standard 184-18)
  - Manuscript editing files, 1990 - 1998; F-184-4-3; 50 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of draft manuscripts, annotated with editors' revisions, and copyeditors and proofreaders marks.
    This sub-series is a group of case files organized by manuscript. The files are arranged alphabetically by author's last name.
    - Beckylane - Where the Rivers Join, 1994; F-184-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 184-19)
    - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Prozac Highway - copy-edit, 1997; F-184-4-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 184-19)
    - Decter, Ann - Paper, Sissors, Rock, 1992; F-184-4-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 184-19)
    - Decter, Ann - Honour, vol. 1, 1996; F-184-4-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 184-19)
    - Decter, Ann - Honour, vol. 2, 1996; F-184-4-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 184-19)
    - Douglas, Marion - Bending at the Bow - copy-edit, 1995; F-184-4-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 184-19)
    - Lai, Larissa - When Fox Is a Thousand - copy-edit, vol. 1, 1995; F-184-4-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 184-20)
    - Lai, Larissa - When Fox Is a Thousand - copy-edit, vol. 2, 1995; F-184-4-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 184-20)
    - Lai, Larissa - When Fox Is a Thousand - second draft edited ms, vol. 1, 1995; F-184-4-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 184-20)
    - Lai, Larissa - When Fox Is a Thousand - second draft edited ms, vol. 2, 1995; F-184-4-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 184-20)
    - Lee, SKY - Bellydancer, [199-?]; F-184-4-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 184-20)
    - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night - copy-edit, vol. 1, 1997; F-184-4-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 184-20)
    - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night - copy-edit, vol. 2, 1997; F-184-4-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 184-21)
    - Mootoo, Shani - Cereus Blooms at Night - copy-edit, vol. 3, 1997; F-184-4-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 184-21)
    - Taste This - Boys Like Her - ready for copy-edit, 1998; F-184-4-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 184-21)
    - Taste This - Boys Like Her - copy-edit, vol. 1, 1998; F-184-4-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 184-21)
    - Taste This - Boys Like Her - copy-edit, vol. 2, 1998; F-184-4-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 184-21)
    - Taste This - Boys Like Her - production, vol. 1, 1998; F-184-4-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 184-21)
    - Taste This - Boys Like Her - production, vol. 2, 1998; F-184-4-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 184-22)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkey Puzzle, vol. 1, 1998; F-184-4-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 184-22)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkey Puzzle, vol. 2, 1998; F-184-4-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 184-22)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkey Puzzle - first draft, 1998; F-184-4-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 184-22)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkey Puzzle - second proof, 1998; F-184-4-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 184-22)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkey Puzzle - second proof - Rita's changes, 1998; F-184-4-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 184-22)
    - Wong, Rita - Monkey Puzzle - production edit, 1998; F-184-4-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 184-22)
  - Submissions and solicitations, 1986 - 1999; F-184-4-4; 25 cm of textual records
    Press Gang Publishers responded to manuscript submissions and book proposals by either declining to publish the material (rejections) or requesting additional material for further evaluation (solicitations). This sub-series consists of records relating to these decisions. Records include correspondence, proposals, manuscript samples, notes, and working papers.
    - Submission guidelines, [199-?]; F-184-4-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 184-23)
    - Correspondence - solicitation, Ts'eku, 1986 - 1989; F-184-4-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 184-23)
    - Correspondence - rejections, general, vol. 1, 1988; F-184-4-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 184-23)
    - Correspondence - rejections, general, vol. 2, 1988; F-184-4-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 184-23)
    - Correspondence - solicitation, Lucille Gilles, Myrna Driol, 1988; F-184-4-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 184-23)
    - Correspondence - solicitation, Greta Nemiroff, 1988 - 1989; F-184-4-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 184-23)
      Nemiroff, Greta; Textual records
    - Correspondence - rejections, general, vol. 1, 1989; F-184-4-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 184-23)
    - Correspondence - rejections, general, vol. 2, 1989; F-184-4-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 184-23)
    - Correspondence - solicitation, Bonny Walford, 1989; F-184-4-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 184-23)
      Walford, Bonny; Textual records
    - Correspondence - solicitation, Jaime Williamson, 1989; F-184-4-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 184-23)
      Williamson, Jaime; Textual records
    - Cover quotes solicited, 1993 - 1996; F-184-4-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 184-23)
    - Manuscript ideas, 1993 - 1997; F-184-4-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 184-24)
    - Manuscript solicitations, 1995 - 1996; F-184-4-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 184-24)
    - Manuscript rejections, vol. 1, 1997; F-184-4-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 184-24)
    - Manuscript rejections, vol. 2, 1997; F-184-4-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 184-24)
    - Manuscript queries, 1998; F-184-4-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 184-24)
    - Manuscript solicitations, 1998; F-184-4-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 184-24)
    - Rejection letters, 1998; F-184-4-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 184-24)
    - Manuscript submissions, 1999; F-184-4-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 184-24)
- Production files, 1976 - 1996; F-184-5; 47 cm of textual records 9 photographs 8 negatives 4 contact sheets; General note: photograph materials are located in files 3, 11, 22, 25, 46 and 53.
  Series consists of records relating to the physical production of books. Activities documented include book and jacket design, proof-reading, costing, and printing. Records include correspondence, contracts and agreements, galleys, mock-ups, photographs, negatives, dust jackets, proof-readers' reports, printing estimates and quotes, order forms, invoices, and purchase orders.
  This series is primarily a group of case files organized by book. The first three files are general files dealing with production. The remaining files are arranged alphabetically by author's last name.
  - General - Press Gang titles: production records, 1983 - 1988; F-184-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
  - General - production and author correspondence, vol. 1, 1992 - 1996; F-184-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
  - General - production and author correspondence (negatives and photographs), vol. 2, 1992 - 1996; F-184-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - small 184-48)
    Textual records; Photographic materials
  - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie - Too Few to Count, 1987; F-184-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
    Ellen Adelberg; Currie, Claudia; Textual records
  - Adelberg, Ellen and Claudia Currie - Too Few to Count, 1987 - 1991; F-184-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
  - Arnott, Joanne - Wiles of Girlhood, 1991; F-184-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
  - Arnott, Joanne - My Grass Cradle, 1992 - 1993; F-184-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
  - Arnott, Joanne - Breasting the Waves, 1995; F-184-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
  - Bank Book Collective - An Account to Settle, 1979; F-184-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
    Bank Book Collective; Textual records
  - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook, vol. 1, 1996; F-184-5-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
  - Blackbridge, Persimmon - Sunnybrook (negative), vol. 2, 1996; F-184-5-0-0-11 (Archival box - small 184-48)
  - Bociurkiw, Marusya - The Woman Who Loved Airports, 1993 - 1994; F-184-5-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
  - Brant, Beth - Food and Spirits, 1991; F-184-5-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
    Brant, Beth; Textual records
  - Briskin, Linda - The Day the Fairies Went on Strike, 1981; F-184-5-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
  - Calendar, 1977; F-184-5-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Calendar and poster projects, 1978; F-184-5-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Cameron, Anne - Daughters of Copper Woman - large print, 1996; F-184-5-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Chrystos - Not Vanishing, 1988 - 1994; F-184-5-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Chrystos - Dream On, 1991 - 1992; F-184-5-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Chrystos - In Her I Am, 1993 - 1996; F-184-5-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Chrystos - Fire Power, vol. 1, 1995; F-184-5-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Chrystos - Fire Power (negative), vol. 2, 1995; F-184-5-0-0-22 (Archival box - small 184-48)
  - Creese, Gillian and Veronica Strong-Boag - British Columbia Reconsidered, 1991 - 1992; F-184-5-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
    Gillian Creese; Strong-Boag, Veronica; Textual records
  - Crossland, Jackie - Collateral Damage, vol. 1, 1992; F-184-5-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
    Crossland, Jackie; Textual records
  - Crossland, Jackie - Collateral Damage (contact sheets), vol. 2, 1992; F-184-5-0-0-25 (Archival box - small 184-48)
  - Decter, Ann - Paper, Scissors, Rock, 1992 - 1993; F-184-5-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Decter, Ann - Honour, 1996; F-184-5-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Diamond, Sara - Women's Labour History Project - correspondence and grant requests, 1981 - 1984; F-184-5-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
    Diamond, Sara; Textual records
  - Diamond, Sara - Women's Labour History Project - working papers, 1981; F-184-5-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Diamond, Sara - Chambermaids and Whistlepunks - pre-production notes, 1985; F-184-5-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Diamond, Sara - Chambermaids and Whistlepunks - backorder and delay forms, 1986; F-184-5-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Douglas, Marion - Bending at the Bow, 1995 - 1996; F-184-5-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
  - Dueck, Lynette - Sing Me No More, 1992; F-184-5-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 184-26)
    Dueck, Lynette; Textual records
  - Ellis, Megan - Surviving Procedures after a Sexual Assault, 1986 - 1989; F-184-5-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
    Megan Ellis; Textual records
  - Faith, Karlene - Unruly Women, 1992 - 1995; F-184-5-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Frank, K. Portland - Anti-Psychiatry Bibliography, 1979; F-184-5-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 184-25)
    K. Portland Frank; Textual records
  - Fuller, Janine and Stuart Blackley - Restricted Entry, 1994 - 1995; F-184-5-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Fuller, Janine and Stuart Blackley - Restricted Entry, 1996; F-184-5-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Jacob, Suzanne - Life, After All, 1988 - 1989; F-184-5-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Jankola, Beth - Jody Said, 1978; F-184-5-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
    Jankola, Beth; Textual records
  - Kellerhals-Stewart, Heather - Muktu, the Backward Muskox, 1983; F-184-5-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
    Kellerhals-Stewart, Heather; Textual records
  - Kiss and Tell - Drawing the Line, 1991 - 1992; F-184-5-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Kiss and Tell - Her Tongue on My Theory, 1994; F-184-5-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Lee, SKY - Bellydancer, vol. 1, 1994; F-184-5-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - McLaughlin, Karen - Choral, vol. 1, 1994; F-184-5-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - McLaughlin, Karen - Choral (negatives), vol. 2, 1994; F-184-5-0-0-46 (Archival box - small 184-48)
  - Moiseiwitsch, Carel - Wonder Woman and the End of the Nuclear Family, 1984; F-184-5-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Mootoo, Shani - Out on Main Street, 1992 - 1994; F-184-5-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Pink Primates Project - Pork Roasts, 1981; F-184-5-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Potrebenko, Helen - Sometimes They Sang - cover design, 1986; F-184-5-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Potrebenko, Helen - Sometimes They Sang, 1996; F-184-5-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Rape poster, vol. 1, 1977; F-184-5-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Rape poster (photographs), vol. 2, 1977; F-184-5-0-0-53 (Archival box - small 184-48)
  - Richler, Nancy - Throwaway Angels, 1996; F-184-5-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 184-27)
  - Silvera, Makeda - Her Head a Village, 1993 - 1994; F-184-5-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
  - Smith, Dorothy E. and Sarah J. David (editors) - Women Look at Psychiatry - cost book, 1976; F-184-5-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
    Dorothy E. Smith; Sarah J. David; Textual records
  - Stonehouse, Cathy - The Words I Know, 1994; F-184-5-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
  - Telling It Book Collective - Telling It, 1990 - 1993; F-184-5-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
    Telling It Book Collective; Textual records
  - Warland, Betsy - Proper Deafinitions, 1990; F-184-5-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
  - Warland, Betsy - Inversions, 1990 - 1992; F-184-5-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
  - Williams, Jana L. - Scuttlebutt, 1990; F-184-5-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
    Jana Williams; Textual records
  - Women's Research Centre - Recollecting Our Lives, 1989 - 1992; F-184-5-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
    Women's Research Centre; Textual records
- Promotion and marketing files, 1975 - 2000; F-184-6; 2.04 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to promoting and marketing the various titles published by Press Gang. Activities, events and topics documented include the preparation of publicity material about authors and books, catalogues of Press Gang titles, book reviews, book fairs, book launches, and authors' tours. Records include reviews and review correspondence, other correspondence, biogaphical material about authors, press releases, flyers, posters, mailing lists, dust jackets, and travel itineraries.
  - Promotion and marketing - general files, 1985 - 1999; F-184-6-1; 42 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the general promotion and marketing of Press Gang titles. Activities, events and topics documented include tours, book launches, and book fairs. Records include correspondence, reviews, flyers, sales kits, and other documents.
    - Promotion: The Women's Press (Canada), 1985 - 1989; F-184-6-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
    - Promotion—various titles, 1987; F-184-6-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
    - Third International Feminist Bookfair, 1988; F-184-6-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
    - Fifth International Feminist Bookfair, 1991; F-184-6-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
    - Promotion—various titles, vol. 1, 1991 - 1998; F-184-6-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
    - Promotion—various titles, vol. 2, 1991 - 1998; F-184-6-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 184-28)
    - Book promotion, tours, vol. 1, 1994; F-184-6-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 184-29)
    - Book promotion, tours, vol. 2, 1994; F-184-6-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 184-29)
    - Reviews—backlist titles, 1994 - 1997; F-184-6-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 184-29)
    - Tours—various titles, 1994 - 1998; F-184-6-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 184-29)
    - Marketing—catalogue mail out, 1995; F-184-6-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 184-29)
    - New titles marketing (fall), 1995; F-184-6-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 184-29)
    - Promotional materials(fall), 1995; F-184-6-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 184-29)
    - U.S. sales information,supplementary(fall), 1995; F-184-6-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 184-29)
    - Book clubs, mail order, 1995 - 1996; F-184-6-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 184-29)
    - Promotion—letters of appraisal or support, 1995 - 1997; F-184-6-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 184-29)
    - WEPA—marketing project U.S., 1996; F-184-6-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 184-29)
    - Promotion—various titles, 1996; F-184-6-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 184-30)
    - Promotional materials(spring), 1996; F-184-6-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 184-30)
    - Sales kit (spring), 1996; F-184-6-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 184-30)
    - Book launch (fall), 1996; F-184-6-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 184-30)